# MUSTAFA RASHID

## **FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER**

I am an experienced full stack web developer. With 4 years of experience in the field, I strive to create the most beautiful, functional, and secure web apps for businesses all around the world. using cutting edge technologies and and state of the art production methodologies.

## SKILLS

- ReactJS
- NEXT.JS
- Tailwind CSS
- Three.JS
- Node.JS

- Express
- API's
- Databases:
  - PostgreSQL
  - o non-relational databases

#### **EDUCATION**

#### LAW FIRM INTERN

Major in international law & public relations University of Tanta | 2020 - 2023

#### CS AND WEB DEVELOPMENT

Course in Web development & Computer Science
Online with various academies and self-teaching routes

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER**

Self employed 2020 - 2023

- Created and managed the online presence for multiple million-dollar companies and startups.
- Created multiple self contained startups with the help of my freelancing team before April - 2021

#### **TEAM LEADER & SUPERVISOR**

Teleperformance EG 2018 - 2021

- Worked as a customer service rep for Teleperformance EG, then got promoted to a supervisor in record-breaking time
- With my management skills, I saw incredible success in leading my team to achieve record breaking numbers

### CONTACT

mustafarashid.cs@gmail.com



in Linkedin



Petrone#5119